January 31, 2020

Dear Employer,

As one of the leading sales figures for ClickEx, I developed key sales material, and hired and trained new sales representatives. I have engaged in consultative on-site sales, telesales, cold-calling, lead generation, proposal writing, marketing, contract negotiations, and after-the-sale support.

A sales professional experienced with procurement, domestic logistics, and delivery of commercial and industrial equipment. From initial contact, to evaluation and proposal submittal, to acquisition and sales, I am experienced with the organizations full sales and management operations.

My verbal and written communication and presentation skills are very strong and my ability to prospect, engage, qualify and close customers is excellent. My selling style is cool, calm and attentive listening to the needs of the customer.

We should make contact in the next 10 days to arrange an interview and discuss the position. Should you have any questions before that time, please feel free to call me at 310-494-6208 or email me at pierpont311@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Cordially,

Fabian Molinero

## Objective

To obtain a position working within a dynamic and thriving company, where my qualifications and professional management skills are challenged and utilized with potential for growth.

## Summary of Skills

Over 10 years' experience in customer service, management, marketing and sales.

Project management experiences such as strategic planning, implementation and coordinating between groups and companies. Strong T.E.A.M. (TOGETHER EVERYONE ACHIEVES MORE) leadership skills, communication, presentation skills combined with exceptional motivational abilities.

Effective communications with clients and colleagues coming from diverse background.

Personal Development: Completed more than 9 sales training and other professional executive programs from trainers and authors, since year 2004.

Fluent in Spanish. Experience in translating and presenting documents for customers.

Experience

Interstate Capital, Inc. Long Beach, CA
Purchasing Director 2015 – Current

Sourcing equipment throughout the US. Submitting proposals for inventory and assets. Scheduling and logistics for sales delivery. Domestic travel about 25 times per year to meet clients. Maintaining the day-to-day relations with customer contacts and overseeing daily operations of assigned projects.

ClickEx, Inc San Diego, CA Sales Operations 2011 – 2015

Prospected new accounts, presented products and services, created long term B2B customers. Coordinating employee activities and schedules. Developed new marketing campaigns and trained call center. Inside sales of 100+ calls per day. Administer vender relations and inventory management

Operations, Budgeting, Marketing, Purchasing, and Business Development.

99 cent plus mart Rialto, CA Co-Owner 2010 – 2011

Managed day-to-day Operations, Budgeting, Marketing, Purchasing, and Business Development.

Coordinating employee activities and schedules

Administer vender relations and inventory management

Better Business Bureau Colton, CA Account Manager 2008 – 2010

Open new accounts through cold calling and business to business prospecting. Managing accounts and retention. Primarily inside sales 100+ calls per day

Fortune Hi-Tech Marketing Emeryville, CA Executive Sales Manager 2005 – 2008 Develop and execute effective marketing strategies.

Decisively deal with problems and that arise in our daily work routine.

Help and teach team members develop personally and professionally.

Obtain new account leads through networking, and grew existing relationships in the large business sector.

Review and help with the writing of proposals for funding and strategy.

Our solid sales T.E.A.M. Increased sales 28% in 2006.

## Education

Mt. San Jacinto Community College

Computer Science

University of California, Berkeley

**Business Administration** 

Skills

Bilingual (Span/Eng), Office, QuickBooks POS, Adobe Suite, HTML, Java, Python, C#, IntelliJ, VS Code, Android Studio, SEO, TeamViewer, and beyond.